Welcome [music] to this expense agent
video series. In this video, we will
explain brand new web app experience.
So, the main idea is that expense agent
move from ERP experience into AI
experience. So, what is there new? In
general, you're not supposed to have
this central license at all. We are
trying to follow where you actually
work. So, only what you need to have is
your enter ID and you can log in into
web app without any problem. You can
capture all your receipts, you can
submit, you can work without any
problem.
But, when we talk about this web app,
actually web app is UI for expense agent
because expense agent will work on
behalf of you. And now, we will explain
in a short demo how you can easily use
it.
>> Thank you, Alexander.
So, let me show you the web experience
that we have built for expense agent. To
access this web experience, you have to
go to app.expenses.dynamics.com.
Once the administrator in your
organization has already set up the
expense agent inside Business Central.
So, let me go full screen and show you
how it works. So, this is a new
intuitive easy-to-use experience
dedicated for all the employees in the
organization
uh for the expense management. And these
employees do not need to be aware about
the accounting knowledge and hence
therefore this expense management
dedicated portal is easy to use. They do
not even need Business Central license
as Alexander already mentioned. So, let
me just show you how easy it is to
access these.
So, let's just take one of the receipts
here and we can also do multiple
selection.
And then, that is it. Now, the agent
will take care of it and it is already
started processing these receipts
uh on the side you can see. While the
agent is processing, let's just see how
it looks like in the expense report.
In this case, the there is an expense
report that multiple expenses that has
been already extracted and processed by
the expense agent. So, let me just show
you how it looks like. We can deep dive
into individual expenses and in here you
can see the receipt that was uploaded to
the agent uh in the zoomed view and you
can see all the data that was extracted
by the agent automatically from the
receipt. All the important data
including merchant amount date, but also
not only that the agent has went a step
ahead and it has done the appropriate
categorization of the receipt based on
the context of the receipt. So, in this
case it's a taxi receipt, so it has
decided to do the categorization for
ground transport.
And while we have seen this receipt, the
agent has also processed the receipts
that we uploaded uh already.
So, let me just go to another expense
within this report.
And here we can see that this is
actually a hotel receipt with a lot of
itemization in it. So, in this case the
agent has categorized it correctly,
extracted all the appropriate amount,
but it has also decided and went ahead
based on the administration settings in
the Business Central to itemized all the
list. So, no more manually needing to
enter all these uh lines individually.
And if if something is incorrect or
something needs to be changed, you can
go ahead and edit one of these things
and uh and change the appropriate
category or sub amount if needed. But
agent automatically does it, so it's in
most of the cases no editing would be
required.
In this web experience beyond the
itemization, categorization, and
extraction, uh there is another feature
where agent automatically determines if
the expenses are actually compliant or
non-compliant based on the rules and
policy settings inside the Business
Central that your administrator have
configured. So, in this case you can see
for example uh
that uh
in one of the receipt it is requiring us
to add a add more details and we can
just easily go ahead and fix and add
more details and then uh and then close
it and make it compliant.
I would like to mention that the expense
agent in this case actually handles all
the receipts, be it PDF images and it
also supports multiple different types
and categories of expenses, mileage, per
diem and so on. So, it is very intuitive
to use and user can just go ahead and
click on submit and that is it.
>> Thank you, Monica.
So, it was a short video how you can
easily use new web app for expense
agent. So, thank you for watching this
video and we really hope you will start
using this new
uh feature as soon as possible.
>> Thank you.